iprofindia.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy

(a) By accessing or using the Site you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information. To enable you to become a registered User of our Site and / or subscriber of our products / services, we need to have your basic personal Information. Apart from this, when you visit our site, our systems collect details about your computer?s personal information like your IP address. However, your IP address does not identify you personally. ?Personal Information? refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person, to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, identification number and credit card information.

(b) All the information collected via the Site shall be treated as key business assets of iProf. As applicable, the information collected by iProf shall be used to contact you about the Site and related news and services; to monitor and improve the Site; to calculate the number of Users to the Site and to know the geographical locations of the Users; to update you on all the special offers available on the Site and provide you with a better experience.

(c) Please note that when you place an order, some of your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties in order to enable them and iProf to perform their duties and fulfill your order requirements.

(d) iProf may, with or without notice to you, disclose Personal Information in order to respond to court orders or other legal processes or any tax authorities.

(e) iProf utilizes a standard technology called 'cookies' and web server logs to collect information regarding the use of the Site. 'Cookies' is a small file containing a string of characters that are sent to your computer, which uniquely identifies your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

(f) If you choose to participate in a special event (for example, a promotion or contest) conducted by iProf, iProf may share your Personal Information provided by you with the third party partners conducting such an event. In such cases, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out, and not have your Personal Information shared with such third party partners.
